mebeam.com 2014-02-09

# CuSeeMe.tv | Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy for cuseeme.tv_**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at apakian@gmail.com.   
At cuseeme.tv, the privacy of our visitors is of extremely important. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by cuseeme.tv and how it is used. 

**_Log Files_**  
Like many other Web sites, cuseeme.tv makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**_Cookies and Web Beacons_**  
cuseeme.tv does not use cookies. 

**_DoubleClick DART Cookie_**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on cuseeme.tv.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to cuseeme.tv and other sites on the Internet.  
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at - [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners is Google Adsense 

Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the ads that you see. 

cuseeme.tv has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
